<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns1:FunctionalResource xmlns:ns1="http://iso.org.dod.ccsds">
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF VisibleString (SIZE (30 .. 256))" name="service-instance-identifier" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the identifier of the given service instance. " oidBit="1"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   timely-online   (0)&#xA;,   complete-online   (1)&#xA;,   offline   (2)&#xA;}" name="delivery-mode" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the delivery mode of the given RAF service instance. It can take on three values:&#xA;- 'timely online'  - the timely online delivery mode limits the size of the backlog of not yet delivered data that is allowed to accumulate by discarding data that cannot be delivered within a certain time. Furthermore, when data is discarded, it is discarded ‘in&#xA;chunks’, i.e., as a sufficiently large block of contiguous frames rather than as random frames here and there; in general, this approach maximizes the usefulness of the data that is delivered.&#xA;- 'complete online' - this delivery mode attempts to deliver all acquired frames having the user selected characteristics, in order, with minimum delay consistent with the available ground communications bandwidth. To that end, the service provider has a buffer sufficiently large to deal with communications service delays, outages, and bandwidth limitations;&#xA;- 'offline' - in this delivery mode, the provider side buffer enables data to be delivered hours or days after their acquisition. To that end, this buffer is sufficiently large to hold all data that might be accumulated during several space link sessions." oidBit="2"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 600)" name="return-timeout-period" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the setting of the maximum time period in seconds permitted from when a confirmed RAF operation is invoked until the return is received by the invoker." oidBit="3"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 100)" name="latency-limit" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the maximum allowable delivery latency time, in seconds, for the online delivery modes, i.e., the maximum delay from when the frame is acquired by the provider until it is delivered to the user: This parameter shall be flagged as undefined if delivery-mode = 'offline'." oidBit="4"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 1000)" name="transfer-buffer-size" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the number of frames the provider shall block in one RAF-PDU before passing it to the underlying communications layer except if expiry of latency-limit requires earlier release of the RAF-PDU. If delivery-mode = 'offline', latency-limit has no effect." oidBit="5"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SET (SIZE (1 .. 3)) OF SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   good   (0)&#xA;,   erred   (1)&#xA;,   all   (2)&#xA;}" name="permitted-frame-quality" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the set of the quality of the frames that the user may select with the given RAF service instance. The permitted frame quality settings must be chosen from the following set of values: &#xA;- 'good' - only frames that based on successful RS decoding/correcting or, in the absence of RS encoding, based on the check of the FECF are assumed to be error free will be delivered to the user;&#xA;- 'erred' - only frames that based on unsuccessful RS decoding/correcting or, in the absence of RS encoding, based on the failed check of the FECF were found to contain errors will be delivered to the user;&#xA;- 'all'  - all frames regardless if error free or not are delivered to the user; this includes telemetry frames for which due to lack of compatibility with the pertinent CCSDS Recommendations the quality cannot be determined." oidBit="6"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   unbound   (0)&#xA;,   ready   (1)&#xA;,   active   (2)&#xA;}" name="si-state" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the status of the given instance of the RAF service. It can take on the following values:&#xA;- 'unbound' - All resources required to enable the provision of the RAF service have been allocated, and all objects required to provide the service have been instantiated; however, no association yet exists between the user and the provider, i.e., the RAF transfer service provider port is not bound;&#xA;- 'ready'- An association has been established between the user and the provider, and they may interact by means of the service operations. However, sending of telemetry frames from the provider to the user (by means of the RAF-TRANSFER-DATA operation) is not permitted; the user may enable the delivery of telemetry frames by means of the appropriate service operation (RAF-START), which, in turn, will cause the provider to transition to the state 'active';&#xA;- 'active' -  This state resembles state ‘ready’, except that now the provider will send telemetry frames provided frames of the selected characteristics are made available by the RAF production process; the service continues in this state until the user invokes the RAF-STOP operation to cause the provider to suspend delivery of telemetry frames and transition back to state 'ready' or the PEER-ABORT invocation to cause the service to transition back to the 'unbound' state." oidBit="7"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 600)" name="reporting-cycle" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the current setting of the time in seconds between successive RAF-STATUS-REPORT invocations sent by the RAF service provider. The permissible values are in the range (2 .. 600). If cyclic reporting is off, the value reported is zero." oidBit="8"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   running   (0)&#xA;,   interrupted   (1)&#xA;,   halted   (2)&#xA;}" name="production-status" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the status of the service production process used by the given instance of an RAF service. It can take on the following values:&#xA;- 'running' - the RAF production process is capable of processing a return space link physical channel, if available;&#xA;- 'interrupted' - the RAF production process is stopped due to a fault;&#xA;- 'halted' - the RAF production process is stopped and production equipment is out of service due to management action." oidBit="9"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   good   (0)&#xA;,   erred   (1)&#xA;,   all   (2)&#xA;}" name="requested-frame-quality" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the quality of the frames that shall be delivered by the given RAF service instance. It can take on three values:&#xA;- 'good' - only frames that based on successful RS decoding/correcting or, in the absence of RS encoding, based on the check of the FECF are assumed to be error free will be delivered to the user;&#xA;- 'erred' - only frames that based on unsuccessful RS decoding/correcting or, in the absence of RS encoding, based on the failed check of the FECF were found to contain errors will be delivered to the user;&#xA;- 'all'  - all frames regardless if error free or not are delivered to the user; this includes telemetry frames for which due to lack of compatibility with the pertinent CCSDS Recommendations the quality cannot be determined.&#xA;If the given service instance does not constrain this parameter to a single value, it shall be flagged 'undefined' whenever si-state ≠ 'active'." oidBit="10"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned" name="number-of-error-free-frames-delivered" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the  total number of telemetry frames that were annotated with a frame-quality of ‘good’ and delivered to the user since the start of the service instance provision period." oidBit="11"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned" name="number-of-frames-delivered" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the  total number of telemetry frames that were delivered to the user since the start of the service instance provision period." oidBit="12"/>
</ns1:FunctionalResource>