<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ns1:FunctionalResource xmlns:ns1="http://iso.org.dod.ccsds">
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF VisibleString (SIZE (30 .. 256))" name="service-instance-identifier" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the identifier of the given service instance. " oidBit="1"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   timely-online   (0)&#xA;,   complete-online   (1)&#xA;,   offline   (2)&#xA;}" name="delivery-mode" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the delivery mode of the given RCF service instance. It can take on three values:&#xA;- 'timely online'  - the timely online delivery mode limits the size of the backlog of not yet delivered data that is allowed to accumulate by discarding data that cannot be delivered within a certain time. Furthermore, when data is discarded, it is discarded ‘in&#xA;chunks’, i.e., as a sufficiently large block of contiguous frames rather than as random frames here and there; in general, this approach maximizes the usefulness of the data that is delivered.&#xA;- 'complete online' - this delivery mode attempts to deliver all acquired frames having the user selected characteristics, in order, with minimum delay consistent with the available ground communications bandwidth. To that end, the service provider has a buffer sufficiently large to deal with communications service delays, outages, and bandwidth limitations;&#xA;- 'offline' - in this delivery mode, the provider side buffer enables data to be delivered hours or days after their acquisition. To that end, this buffer is sufficiently large to hold all data that might be accumulated during several space link sessions." oidBit="2"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 600)" name="return-timeout-period" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the setting of the maximum time period in seconds permitted from when a confirmed RCF operation is invoked until the return is received by the invoker." oidBit="3"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 100)" name="latency-limit" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the maximum allowable delivery latency time, in seconds, for the online delivery modes, i.e., the maximum delay from when the frame is acquired by the provider until it is delivered to the user: this parameter shall be flagged as undefined if delivery-mode = 'offline'." oidBit="4"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (1 .. 100)" name="transfer-buffer-size" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the number of frames the provider shall block in one RCF-PDU before passing it to the underlying communications layer except if expiry of latency-limit requires earlier release of the RCF-PDU. If delivery-mode = 'offline', latency-limit has no effect." oidBit="5"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SET OF SEQUENCE (SIZE (3)) OF IntUnsigned, where &#xA;the first element is the SCID (0 .. 1023), &#xA;the second element is the TFVN (0 .. 1); and &#xA;the third element is the VCID (0 .. 63).&#xA;As to have a way for expressing also the selection of the Master Channel, the 'special' VCID value 99 is used to indicate that the VCID may have any value. Therefore the exact range specification is:&#xA;VCID ϵ {0 .. 63,99}    " name="permitted-global-vcid-set " SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the set of Master and/or Virtual Channel that the given RCF service instance permits the user to select. The parameter is a set of the concatenation of the CCSDS assigned Spacecraft Identifier (SCID), the Transfer Frame Version Number (TFVN) and, if applicable, the Virtual Channel Identifier (VCID). The range of the Spacecraft Identifier and the Virtual Channel Identifier depend on the TFVN as follows:&#xA;- TFVN = 0 (version 1) - SCID = (0 .. 1023)10, VCID = (0 .. 7)10;&#xA;- TFVN = 1 (version 2) - SCID = (0 .. 255)10, VCID = (0 .. 63)10." oidBit="6"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   unbound   (0)&#xA;,   ready   (1)&#xA;,   active   (2)&#xA;}" name="si-state" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the status of the given instance of the RCF service. It can take on the following values:&#xA;- 'unbound' - All resources required to enable the provision of the RCF service have been allocated, and all objects required to provide the service have been instantiated; however, no association yet exists between the user and the provider, i.e., the RCF transfer service provider port is not bound;&#xA;- 'ready'- An association has been established between the user and the provider, and they may interact by means of the service operations. However, sending of telemetry frames from the provider to the user (by means of the RCF-TRANSFER-DATA operation) is not permitted; the user may enable the delivery of telemetry frames by means of the appropriate service operation (RCF-START), which, in turn, will cause the provider to transition to the state 'active';&#xA;- 'active' -  This state resembles state ‘ready’, except that now the provider will send telemetry frames provided frames of the selected characteristics are made available by the RCF production process; the service continues in this state until the user invokes the RCF-STOP operation to cause the provider to suspend delivery of telemetry frames and transition back to state 'ready' or the PEER-ABORT invocation to cause the service to transition back to the 'unbound' state." oidBit="7"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 600)" name="reporting-cycle" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the current setting of the time in seconds between successive RCF-STATUS-REPORT invocations sent by the RCF service provider. The permissible values are in the range (2 .. 600). If cyclic reporting is off, the value reported is zero." oidBit="8"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned (0 .. 2)&#xA;{   running   (0)&#xA;,   interrupted   (1)&#xA;,   halted   (2)&#xA;}" name="production-status" SemanticDefinition="This enumerated parameter reports the status of the service production process used by the given instance of an RCF service. It can take on the following values:&#xA;- 'running' - the RCF production process is capable of processing a return link Master or Virtual Channel, if available;&#xA;- 'interrupted' - the RCF production process is stopped due to a fault;&#xA;- 'halted' - the RCF production process is stopped and production equipment is out of service due to management action." oidBit="9"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (3)) OF IntUnsigned, where &#xA;the first element is the SCID (0 .. 1023), &#xA;the second element is the TFVN (0 .. 1); and &#xA;the third element is the VCID (0 .. 63).&#xA;As to have a way for expressing also the selection of the Master Channel, the 'special' VCID value 99 is used to indicate that the VCID may have any value. Therefore the exact range specification is:&#xA;VCID ϵ {0 .. 63,99}    " name="requested-global-vcid" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the Master or Virtual Channel that the given RCF service instance shall deliver to the user. The parameter is a concatenation of the CCSDS assigned Spacecraft Identifier (SCID), the Transfer Frame Version Number (TFVN) and, if applicable, the Virtual Channel Identifier (VCID). The range of the Spacecraft Identifier and the Virtual Channel Identifier depend on the TFVN as follows:&#xA;- TFVN = 0 (version 1) - SCID = (0 .. 1023)10, VCID = (0 .. 7)10;&#xA;- TFVN = 1 (version 2) - SCID = (0 .. 255)10, VCID = (0 .. 63)10.&#xA;If the global VCID is not constrained to a single value by the given RCF service instance (see permitted-global-vcid-set), then this parameter shall be flagged undefined as long as si-state ≠ 'active." oidBit="10"/>
	<parameter typeDefinition="SEQUENCE (SIZE (1)) OF IntUnsigned" name="number-of-frames-delivered" SemanticDefinition="This parameter reports the  total number of telemetry frames that were delivered to the user since the start of the service instance provision period." oidBit="11"/>
</ns1:FunctionalResource>